# Stuart Kinnear

54 Lowbridge Court, Garston, Liverpool, L19 2JP 07735872172

stobart13@gmail.com

www.stuartkinnear.co.uk

www.github.com/Stobart13

# **Personal statement**

A highly motivated recent Computer Science graduate who is seeking a job in the Information Technology sector with a willingness to learn and develop all skills. A competent communicator, comfortable working as part of a team or as an individual.

Outside of the professional sphere, a competent team player and excellent communicator, which can be displayed with over 10 years of experience playing Rugby Union.

# **Core skills**

- Excellent communication and team working skills
- Competent in HTML and CSS
- Competent in SQL and MySQL
- Competent in GIT
- Competent in PHP
- Experience with Agile
- Some experience in NoSQL Databases (Such as MongoDB and Firebase)
- Some experience in JavaScript, including Angular
- Some experience in C++ and C#
- Some experience in Java
- Some experience in MVC, ASP.NET Web Forms

# **Employment history**

# **Graduate Software Developer – WSP, Liverpool**

(July 2018 – Present)

### **Duties**

- Working with a team of developers
- Assisting with Support Requests
- Developing Websites using MVC and ASP.Net Web Forms
- Producing Reports using SQL Server Reporting Services

# Bar Staff - Granny Annies Group, Ballymena

(February 2018 –June 2018)

Working in a busy bar environment, working with a team of bar staff and management

### **Duties**

- Cash handling
- General housekeeping
- Liaising with customers
- Refilling stock
- Serve drinks and food to customers

# Garden Centre Assistant - Creative Gardens, Galgorm Castle

(September 2017 – January 2018)

### **Duties**

- Cash Handling
- Liaising with customers and management
- General housekeeping
- Working with other departments on request

# Junior QA Analyst - Synergy Learning, Holywood

(August 2016 – August 2017)

#### **Duties**

- Providing QA on Moodle, Totara and Mahara eLearning themes
- Report to Project Manager and Project Developer(s)

- Working as part as QA team
- Email/Phone Interaction with clients.
- Produce User Documentation for clients when requested
- Also working as part of the Front-End Development team when required.
- Working as part of the Project Management team when required.

# Customer Advisor – Argos, Ballymena

(October 2012 – July 2016)

### **Duties**

- Cash Handling
- Working in Front of House as well as in stock room
- Housekeeping
- Interacting with Customers

# **Education**

# **Ulster University, Coleraine**

(2014 - 2018)

BSc (Hons) in Computing (Internet Systems) with Diploma in Professional Practice – Second Class Honours Upper Division (2:1)

Personal Website (2018) – A personal project which involved designing and developing a website to showcase skills, developed in HTML, JavaScript and CSS. Can be viewed on http://www.stuartkinnear.co.uk/

Final Year Project (2018) – Timetable Application for Ulster University students, created using PHP, MySQL, HTML, JavaScript, CSS and Bootstrap. Can be viewed on http://www.github.com/Stobart13/uuctimetable.

Game Development (2017) – Developed a simple item collection game using Unity and C#. C# was used to control player and AI movement, as well as control aspects such as health, score etc.

StoreSim (2015) – A university assignment developed in Java which used Threads, Buffers

and the Sleep Function, to monitor people entering and leaving a store.

Microsoft Imagine Cup (2015) – EasySpell mobile application. Windows Phone application developed in C# for Children with dyslexia. Consists of three games all with varying difficulty.

Java Calculator (2015) – Created a calculator application using Java and Swin.

# Cambridge House Grammar School, Ballymena

(2007 - 2014)

A Level Information Technology (C) Media Studies (C) Business Studies (B) 8 GCSEs C grade and above (including Maths and English)

# **References**

#### **Peter Hinds**

**Head of Operations** 

Synergy Learning

1 Innis Court

Holywood

BT18 9HF

### 028 9042 2000

peter.hinds@synergy-learning.com

# **Kimberly Bellew**

General Manager

Spinning Mill

17-21 Broughshane Street

Ballymena

**BT43 7AE** 

### hello@grannyannies.co.uk

028 2563 8985